<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>cve_news</title>
    <link>https://www.cve.org/Media/News/AllNews</link>
    <description>Latest posts from https://www.cve.org/Media/News/AllNews. follow.is: feedId:72158581942748160+userId:71370844472670208</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 02:00:55 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Vulnerability Data Enrichment for CVE Records: 230 CNAs on the Enrichment Recognition List for July 7, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/Media/News/item/blog/2025/07/08/CNA-Enrichment-Recognition-List-Update</link>
      <description>Vulnerability Data Enrichment for CVE Records: 230 CNAs on the Enrichment Recognition List for July 7, 2025blogBy CVE Program|July 8, 2025</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Altium Added as CVE Numbering Authority (CNA)</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/Media/News/item/news/2025/07/08/Altium-Added-as-CNA</link>
      <description>Altium Added as CVE Numbering Authority (CNA)newsJuly 8, 2025Altiumis now aCVE Numbering Authority (CNA)for vulnerabilities in the following Altium products only: Altium Designer, A365, Octopart, and Altium Enterprise Server.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minutes from CVE Board Teleconference Meeting on June 11 Now Available</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/Media/News/item/news/2025/07/15/CVE-Board-Minutes-from-June-11</link>
      <description>Minutes from CVE Board Teleconference Meeting on June 11 Now AvailablenewsJuly 15, 2025TheCVE Boardheld a teleconference meeting on June 11, 2025. Read themeeting minutes summary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minutes from CVE Board Teleconference Meeting on June 25 Now Available</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/Media/News/item/news/2025/07/15/CVE-Board-Minutes-from-June-25</link>
      <description>Minutes from CVE Board Teleconference Meeting on June 25 Now AvailablenewsJuly 15, 2025TheCVE Boardheld a teleconference meeting on June 25, 2025. Read themeeting minutes summary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE Record Dispute Policy Updated</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/Media/News/item/news/2025/07/15/CVE-Record-Dispute-Policy-Updated</link>
      <description>CVE Record Dispute Policy UpdatednewsJuly 15, 2025The CVE Program is excited to announce updates to the “CVE Program Policy and Procedure for Disputing a CVE Record” aimed at providing greater clarity and transparency for all parties involved. Approved by theCVE Boardon July 2, 2025, the updated policy is effective immediately and includes streamlined procedures and clearer definitions to address community concerns.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TYPO3 Added as CVE Numbering Authority (CNA)</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/Media/News/item/news/2025/07/15/TYPO3-Added-as-CNA</link>
      <description>TYPO3 Added as CVE Numbering Authority (CNA)newsJuly 15, 2025TYPO3 Associationis now aCVE Numbering Authority (CNA)for vulnerabilities in TYPO3 open-source products only, including TYPO3 CMS core and 3rd party extensions for TYPO3, unless covered by the scope of another CNA.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CERT@VDE Is Now a Root in the CVE Program</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/Media/News/item/blog/2025/07/15/CERTVDE-Is-Now-a-Root-in-the</link>
      <description>CERT@VDE Is Now a Root in the CVE ProgramblogBy CVE Program|July 15, 2025TheCVE Programis expanding its partnership withCERT@VDEfor managing the assignment ofCVE Identifiers (CVE IDs)and publication ofCVE Recordsfor the CVE Program. CERT@VDE is now designated as aRootfor organizations that are cooperative partners of CERT@VDE.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minutes from CVE Board Teleconference Meeting on July 9 Now Available</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/Media/News/item/news/2025/07/22/CVE-Board-Minutes-from-July-9</link>
      <description>Minutes from CVE Board Teleconference Meeting on July 9 Now AvailablenewsJuly 22, 2025TheCVE Boardheld a teleconference meeting on July 9, 2025. Read themeeting minutes summary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TCS-CERT Added as CVE Numbering Authority (CNA)</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/Media/News/item/news/2025/07/22/TCS-CERT-Added-as-CNA</link>
      <description>TCS-CERT Added as CVE Numbering Authority (CNA)newsJuly 22, 2025TCS-CERT(Thales Cyber Solutions Customer’s CERT) is now aCVE Numbering Authority (CNA)for vulnerabilities related to TCS-CERT’s customers’ environment and vulnerabilities related to research conducted by Cyber Solutions by Thales’ Intrusion and Application Security Team.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Rust Project Added as CVE Numbering Authority (CNA)</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/Media/News/item/news/2025/07/22/The-Rust-Project-Added-as-CNA</link>
      <description>The Rust Project Added as CVE Numbering Authority (CNA)newsJuly 22, 2025The Rust Projectis now aCVE Numbering Authority (CNA)for repositories, packages, and websites maintained by the Rust Project. More details:https://www.rust-lang.org/policies/security#scope.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
