<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>cve_news</title>
    <link>https://www.cve.org/Media/News/AllNews</link>
    <description>Latest posts from https://www.cve.org/Media/News/AllNews. follow.is: feedId:72158581942748160+userId:71370844472670208</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jan 2026 01:57:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Vulnerability Data Enrichment for CVE Records: 256 CNAs on the Enrichment Recognition List for December 1, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/Media/News/item/blog/2025/12/02/CNA-Enrichment-Recognition-List-Update</link>
      <description>Vulnerability Data Enrichment for CVE Records: 256 CNAs on the Enrichment Recognition List for December 1, 2025blogBy CVE Program|December 2, 2025</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>runZero, Inc. Added as CVE Numbering Authority (CNA)</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/Media/News/item/news/2025/12/09/runZero-Added-as-CNA</link>
      <description>runZero, Inc. Added as CVE Numbering Authority (CNA)newsDecember 9, 2025runZero, Inc.is now aCVE Numbering Authority (CNA)for vulnerabilities in runZero products, as well as vulnerabilities discovered by, or reported to, runZero that are not in another CNA’s scope.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minutes from CVE Board Teleconference Meeting on November 12 Now Available</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/Media/News/item/news/2025/12/16/CVE-Board-Minutes-from-November-12</link>
      <description>Minutes from CVE Board Teleconference Meeting on November 12 Now AvailablenewsDecember 16, 2025TheCVE Boardheld a teleconference meeting on November 12, 2025. Read themeeting minutes summary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>“Vulnogram User Guide” for CNAs Updated</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/Media/News/item/news/2025/12/16/Vulnogram-User-Guide-for-CNAs-Updated</link>
      <description>“Vulnogram User Guide” for CNAs UpdatednewsDecember 16, 2025The community-developed “Vulnogram User Guide” (PDF, 4.0MB) forCVE Numbering Authorities (CNAs)was updated on December 19, 2025. A “live” version of this document isavailable for CNAs on Google Docs, which continues to be reviewed and updated over time.The guide was updated to add a note in the “Getting Started” section that Chrome 142 introduced a security permission setting that controlslocal network access, which may impact service workers used in Vulnogram. As a result, users may or may not be prompted, and may need to grant local network access to Vulnogram (or globally), to enable service workers and CVE Services login.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINAL WEEK! — Call for Speakers forVulnCon 2026Closes on December 22, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/Media/News/item/blog/2025/12/16/VulnCon-2026-Call-Speakers-Closes-December-22</link>
      <description>FINAL WEEK! — Call for Speakers forVulnCon 2026Closes on December 22, 2025blogBy CVE Program|December 16, 2025CVE/FIRST VulnCon 2026</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE Record Disputes, Explained: A Community Path to Clearer Vulnerability Data in a Compliance-Driven World</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/Media/News/item/blog/2025/12/16/CVE-Record-Disputes-Explained</link>
      <description>CVE Record Disputes, Explained: A Community Path to Clearer Vulnerability Data in a Compliance-Driven WorldblogBy Council of Roots|December 16, 2025In a global program as broad and dynamic asCVE, differences in interpretation are inevitable. One area where these differences occasionally surface is in the determination of whether a reported issue constitutes a vulnerability, and how that determination should be reflected in aCVE Records. CVE Program policy exists precisely to navigate those moments of disagreement — constructively, transparently, and in service of the broader cybersecurity ecosystem.In recentCouncil of Rootsdiscussions, participants have debated the nuances of how disputes are managed within the CVE Program, where there are current challenges, and how they might be best resolved. The conversation reflected a healthy diversity of perspectives and a shared recognition that handling disputes thoughtfully is essential to maintaining both accuracy and trust in CVE data.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>39,080 CVE Records Used as Basis for the “2025 CWE Top 25 Most Dangerous Software Weaknesses List”</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/Media/News/item/blog/2026/01/06/CVE-Records-Basis-2025-CWE-Top-25</link>
      <description>39,080 CVE Records Used as Basis for the “2025 CWE Top 25 Most Dangerous Software Weaknesses List”blogBy CVE Program|January 6, 2026The2025 CWE Top 25 Most Dangerous Software Weaknesseslist was released by theCommon Weakness Enumeration (CWE™) Programon December 11, 2025. The newly released list highlights the most severe and prevalent weaknesses behind the39,080 CVE Records mapped in the 2025 dataset.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Register Now forCVE/FIRST VulnCon 2026on April 13-16, 2026!</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/Media/News/item/blog/2026/01/06/Register-Now-for-VulnCon-2026</link>
      <description>Register Now forCVE/FIRST VulnCon 2026on April 13-16, 2026!blogBy CVE Program|January 6, 2026CVE/FIRST VulnCon 2026</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vulnerability Data Enrichment for CVE Records: 263 CNAs on the Enrichment Recognition List for January 5, 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/Media/News/item/blog/2026/01/06/CNA-Enrichment-Recognition-List-Update</link>
      <description>Vulnerability Data Enrichment for CVE Records: 263 CNAs on the Enrichment Recognition List for January 5, 2026blogBy CVE Program|January 6, 2026</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE Program to Normalize Formatting of Date/Time Fields Across Historical CVE Records Beginning in February 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/Media/News/item/blog/2026/01/06/Historic-CVE-Record-Date-Time-Fields-Normalized</link>
      <description>CVE Program to Normalize Formatting of Date/Time Fields Across Historical CVE Records Beginning in February 2026blogBy CVE Program|January 6, 2026TheCVE™ Programis planning to begin normalizing the formatting of date/time fields across historicalCVE Recordsin February 2026 (see the “Timeline” section below). This update will align older records with the standardized format already used for all new and updated records since February 2025:</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
