<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>cve_news</title>
    <link>https://www.cve.org/Media/News/AllNews</link>
    <description>Latest posts from https://www.cve.org/Media/News/AllNews. follow.is: feedId:72158581942748160+userId:71370844472670208</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 01:51:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Call for Speakers forVulnCon 2026Open Until December 22, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/Media/News/item/blog/2025/11/18/VulnCon-2026-Call-Speakers-Closes-December-22</link>
      <description>Call for Speakers forVulnCon 2026Open Until December 22, 2025blogBy CVE Program|November 18, 2025TheCVE ProgramandFIRSTwill co-hostVulnCon 2026at the DoubleTree Resort by Hilton Hotel Paradise Valley – Scottsdale, in Scottsdale, Arizona, USA, on April 13-16, 2026. TheCall for Speakersdeadlineis December 22, 2025. See detailshere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE Program Expands Partnership with European Union Agency for Cybersecurity (ENISA)—ENISA Is Now a Root in the CVE Program</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/Media/News/item/blog/2025/11/20/ENISA-Root-CVE-Program</link>
      <description>CVE Program Expands Partnership with European Union Agency for Cybersecurity (ENISA)—ENISA Is Now a Root in the CVE ProgramblogBy CVE Program|November 20, 2025TheCVE Programis expanding its partnership with theEuropean Union Agency for Cybersecurity (ENISA)for managing the assignment ofCVE Identifiers (CVE IDs)and publication ofCVE Recordsfor the CVE Program. ENISA is now designated as aRootfor EU member states/EU authorities, EU CSIRTs network members, and cooperative partners under ENISA’s mandate, as well as otherCVE Numbering Authorities (CNAs)who choose ENISA as their Root. Read the ENISAnews release.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE Program Report for Quarter 3 Calendar Year (Q3 CY) 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/Media/News/item/blog/2025/12/02/CVE-Program-Report-for-Q3-2025</link>
      <description>CVE Program Report for Quarter 3 Calendar Year (Q3 CY) 2025blogBy CVE Program|December 2, 2025The CVE Program’s quarterly summary of program milestones and metrics for Q3 CY 2025.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REMINDER: Call for Speakers forVulnCon 2026Closes on December 22, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/Media/News/item/blog/2025/12/02/VulnCon-2026-Call-Speakers-Closes-December-22</link>
      <description>REMINDER: Call for Speakers forVulnCon 2026Closes on December 22, 2025blogBy CVE Program|December 2, 2025The Call for Speakers (CFS) forCVE/FIRST VulnCon 2026closes onDecember 22, 2025.VulnCon 2026will be held on April 13-16, 2026, at the DoubleTree Resort by Hilton Hotel Paradise Valley – Scottsdale, in Scottsdale, Arizona, USA. Details about theCFSrequirements and submission process are availablehere.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vulnerability Data Enrichment for CVE Records: 256 CNAs on the Enrichment Recognition List for December 1, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/Media/News/item/blog/2025/12/02/CNA-Enrichment-Recognition-List-Update</link>
      <description>Vulnerability Data Enrichment for CVE Records: 256 CNAs on the Enrichment Recognition List for December 1, 2025blogBy CVE Program|December 2, 2025</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>runZero, Inc. Added as CVE Numbering Authority (CNA)</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/Media/News/item/news/2025/12/09/runZero-Added-as-CNA</link>
      <description>runZero, Inc. Added as CVE Numbering Authority (CNA)newsDecember 9, 2025runZero, Inc.is now aCVE Numbering Authority (CNA)for vulnerabilities in runZero products, as well as vulnerabilities discovered by, or reported to, runZero that are not in another CNA’s scope.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Minutes from CVE Board Teleconference Meeting on November 12 Now Available</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/Media/News/item/news/2025/12/16/CVE-Board-Minutes-from-November-12</link>
      <description>Minutes from CVE Board Teleconference Meeting on November 12 Now AvailablenewsDecember 16, 2025TheCVE Boardheld a teleconference meeting on November 12, 2025. Read themeeting minutes summary.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>“Vulnogram User Guide” for CNAs Updated</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/Media/News/item/news/2025/12/16/Vulnogram-User-Guide-for-CNAs-Updated</link>
      <description>“Vulnogram User Guide” for CNAs UpdatednewsDecember 16, 2025The community-developed “Vulnogram User Guide” (PDF, 4.0MB) forCVE Numbering Authorities (CNAs)was updated on December 19, 2025. A “live” version of this document isavailable for CNAs on Google Docs, which continues to be reviewed and updated over time.The guide was updated to add a note in the “Getting Started” section that Chrome 142 introduced a security permission setting that controlslocal network access, which may impact service workers used in Vulnogram. As a result, users may or may not be prompted, and may need to grant local network access to Vulnogram (or globally), to enable service workers and CVE Services login.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FINAL WEEK! — Call for Speakers forVulnCon 2026Closes on December 22, 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/Media/News/item/blog/2025/12/16/VulnCon-2026-Call-Speakers-Closes-December-22</link>
      <description>FINAL WEEK! — Call for Speakers forVulnCon 2026Closes on December 22, 2025blogBy CVE Program|December 16, 2025CVE/FIRST VulnCon 2026</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE Record Disputes, Explained: A Community Path to Clearer Vulnerability Data in a Compliance-Driven World</title>
      <link>https://www.cve.org/Media/News/item/blog/2025/12/16/CVE-Record-Disputes-Explained</link>
      <description>CVE Record Disputes, Explained: A Community Path to Clearer Vulnerability Data in a Compliance-Driven WorldblogBy Council of Roots|December 16, 2025In a global program as broad and dynamic asCVE, differences in interpretation are inevitable. One area where these differences occasionally surface is in the determination of whether a reported issue constitutes a vulnerability, and how that determination should be reflected in aCVE Records. CVE Program policy exists precisely to navigate those moments of disagreement — constructively, transparently, and in service of the broader cybersecurity ecosystem.In recentCouncil of Rootsdiscussions, participants have debated the nuances of how disputes are managed within the CVE Program, where there are current challenges, and how they might be best resolved. The conversation reflected a healthy diversity of perspectives and a shared recognition that handling disputes thoughtfully is essential to maintaining both accuracy and trust in CVE data.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
