<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>deeplearning</title>
    <link>https://www.deeplearning.ai/the-batch/</link>
    <description>Latest posts from https://www.deeplearning.ai/the-batch/. follow.is: None</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 02:04:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI’s Five New Models, Hugging Face’s Open Robot, U.S. Tightens Grip on AI Chips, Text-Only LLMs Go Multimodal</title>
      <link>https://www.deeplearning.ai/the-batch/issue-298/</link>
      <description>The Batch AI News and Insights: Even though I’m a much better Python than JavaScript developer, with AI assistance, I’ve been writing a lot of JavaScript code recently.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI’s Hit Image Generator, Hot AI Startups, Better Recommendations, Music Generation for Pros</title>
      <link>https://www.deeplearning.ai/the-batch/issue-299/</link>
      <description>The Batch AI News and Insights: I hope we can empower everyone to build with AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ChatGPT Grovels, Qwen3 Takes on DeepSeek-R1, Johnson &amp; Johnson Reveals AI Strategy, Easy Reasoning Hack</title>
      <link>https://www.deeplearning.ai/the-batch/issue-300/</link>
      <description>The Batch AI News and Insights: I’m delighted to announce that AI Fund has closed $190M for our new fund, in an oversubscribed round.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recipes For Reasoning, Open and Compact Code Generator, Looser AI Regulations, More Factual Output</title>
      <link>https://www.deeplearning.ai/the-batch/issue-301/</link>
      <description>The Batch AI News and Insights: AI’s ability to make tasks not just cheaper, but also faster, is underrated in its importance in creating business value.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Codex’s Robot Dev Team, Grok’s Fixation on South Africa, Saudi Arabia’s AI Power Play, 4-Bit Efficiency With 16-Bit Accuracy</title>
      <link>https://www.deeplearning.ai/the-batch/issue-302/</link>
      <description>The Batch AI News and Insights: In the age of AI, large corporations — not just startups — can move fast. I often speak with large companies’ C-suite and Boards about AI strategy and implementation, and would like to share some ideas that are applicable to big companies.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claude 4 Advances Code Gen, How DeepSeek Built V3 For $5.6m, Google I/O Roundup, O’Reilly Versus OpenAI</title>
      <link>https://www.deeplearning.ai/the-batch/issue-303/</link>
      <description>The Batch AI News and Insights: I am alarmed by the proposed cuts to U.S. funding for basic research, analyzed here, and the impact this would have for U.S. competitiveness in AI and other areas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepSeek-R1 Refreshed, AI’s Energy Conundrum, Agents Get Phished, Machine Translation in Action</title>
      <link>https://www.deeplearning.ai/the-batch/issue-304/</link>
      <description>The Batch AI News and Insights: Everyone can benefit by learning to code with AI! At AI Fund, the venture studio I lead, everyone — not just the engineers — can vibe code or use more sophisticated AI-assisted coding techniques.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FLUX.1 Kontext’s Consistent Characters, Benchmarking Costs Climb, Mary Meeker’s Action-Packed AI Report, Better Video Gen</title>
      <link>https://www.deeplearning.ai/the-batch/issue-305/</link>
      <description>The Batch AI News and Insights: There’s a new breed of GenAI Application Engineers who can build more-powerful applications faster than was possible before, thanks to generative AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apple Sharpens Its GenAI Profile, Hollywood Joins Copyright Fight, OpenAI Ups Reasoning Quotient, LLM Rights Historical Wrongs</title>
      <link>https://www.deeplearning.ai/the-batch/issue-306/</link>
      <description>The Batch AI News and Insights: One of the most effective things the U.S. or any other nation can do to ensure its competitiveness in AI is to welcome high-skilled immigration and international students who have the potential to become high-skilled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Judge Rules Training AI on Copyrighted Works Is Fair Use, Agentic Biology Evolves, Meta Befriends Alexandr Wang</title>
      <link>https://www.deeplearning.ai/the-batch/issue-307/</link>
      <description>The Batch AI News and Insights: On Monday, a United States District Court ruled that training LLMs on copyrighted books constitutes fair use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amazon’s $100 Billion Bet, Meta’s Sensor-Packed Glasses, Anthropic’s Reason-Free Reasoning, Google’s Extreme Weather Prediction</title>
      <link>https://www.deeplearning.ai/the-batch/issue-308/</link>
      <description>The Batch AI News and Insights: I’d like to share a tip for getting more practice building with AI — that is, either using AI building blocks to build applications or using AI coding assistance to create powerful applications quickly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Make LLMs Commit Blackmail, Robotic Beehive, Walmart’s AI App Factory, Training Web Agents</title>
      <link>https://www.deeplearning.ai/the-batch/issue-309/</link>
      <description>The Batch AI News and Insights: Last week, the United States Congress passed President Trump’s “Big Beautiful Bill.” I’m disappointed it didn’t include a proposed moratorium on U.S. state-level AI regulation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Grok Raises Questions, Meta Poaches Talent, California Reframes AI Regulations, Multi-Agent Systems Get Stronger</title>
      <link>https://www.deeplearning.ai/the-batch/issue-310/</link>
      <description>The Batch AI News and Insights: The invention of modern writing instruments like the typewriter made writing easier, but they also led to the rise of writer’s block, where deciding what to write became the bottleneck.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Power Moves in AI Coding, Moonshot’s Agentic LLM, How to Comply with EU AI Regs, AI Agents Evolve</title>
      <link>https://www.deeplearning.ai/the-batch/issue-311/</link>
      <description>The Batch AI News and Insights: We’re organizing a new event called Buildathon: The Rapid Engineering Competition, to be held in the San Francisco Bay Area on Saturday, August 16, 2025!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Resets AI Policy, Qwen3’s Agentic Advance, U.S. Chips for China, The Trouble With AI Friends</title>
      <link>https://www.deeplearning.ai/the-batch/issue-312/</link>
      <description>The Batch AI News and Insights: There is now a path for China to surpass the U.S. in AI. Even though the U.S. is still ahead, China has tremendous momentum with its vibrant open-weights model ecosystem and aggressive moves in semiconductor design and manufacturing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Agentic LLMs Proliferate, Robot Removes Gallbladders, Reasoning Models Boost Emissions, OpenAI Re-Opens</title>
      <link>https://www.deeplearning.ai/the-batch/tag/aug-06-2025/</link>
      <description>The Batch AI News and Insights: Recently Meta made headlines with unprecedented, massive compensation packages for AI model builders exceeding $100M (sometimes spread over multiple years).</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
