<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>deeplearning</title>
    <link>https://www.deeplearning.ai/the-batch/</link>
    <description>Latest posts from https://www.deeplearning.ai/the-batch/. follow.is: None</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 01:48:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Power Moves in AI Coding, Moonshot’s Agentic LLM, How to Comply with EU AI Regs, AI Agents Evolve</title>
      <link>https://www.deeplearning.ai/the-batch/issue-311/</link>
      <description>The Batch AI News and Insights: We’re organizing a new event called Buildathon: The Rapid Engineering Competition, to be held in the San Francisco Bay Area on Saturday, August 16, 2025!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Trump Resets AI Policy, Qwen3’s Agentic Advance, U.S. Chips for China, The Trouble With AI Friends</title>
      <link>https://www.deeplearning.ai/the-batch/issue-312/</link>
      <description>The Batch AI News and Insights: There is now a path for China to surpass the U.S. in AI. Even though the U.S. is still ahead, China has tremendous momentum with its vibrant open-weights model ecosystem and aggressive moves in semiconductor design and manufacturing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open Agentic LLMs Proliferate, Robot Removes Gallbladders, Reasoning Models Boost Emissions, OpenAI Re-Opens</title>
      <link>https://www.deeplearning.ai/the-batch/issue-313/</link>
      <description>The Batch AI News and Insights: Recently Meta made headlines with unprecedented, massive compensation packages for AI model builders exceeding $100M (sometimes spread over multiple years).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GPT-5’s Rough Takeoff, AI Video Blockbusters, India’s Homegrown LLMs, Synthetic Data Generation</title>
      <link>https://www.deeplearning.ai/the-batch/issue-314/</link>
      <description>The Batch AI News and Insights: Just as many businesses are transforming to become more capable by using AI, universities are too.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>China Questions Nvidia, When Models Memorize, Mixture of Video Experts, OpenAI &amp; Oracle Join Forces</title>
      <link>https://www.deeplearning.ai/the-batch/issue-315/</link>
      <description>The Batch AI News and Insights: On Saturday at the Buildathon [http://buildathon.ai] hosted by AI Fund and DeepLearning.AI, over 100 developers competed to build software products quickly using AI assisted coding.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI-Powered Phones Get Proactive, Robot Antelope Joins Herd, LLM Environmental Impacts Get Measured</title>
      <link>https://www.deeplearning.ai/the-batch/issue-316/</link>
      <description>The Batch AI News and Insights: Parallel agents are emerging as an important new direction for scaling up AI. AI capabilities have scaled with more training data, training-time compute, and test-time compute.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gemini’s Environmental Impact, China’s Emerging AI Hub, Chatbot Job Interviews, Security For Agents</title>
      <link>https://www.deeplearning.ai/the-batch/issue-317/</link>
      <description>The Batch AI News and Insights: There is significant unmet demand for developers who understand AI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Stronger Chatbot Guardrails, Weaker Google Monopoly, AI-Assisted Education, 10 Million Tokens of Context</title>
      <link>https://www.deeplearning.ai/the-batch/issue-318/</link>
      <description>The Batch AI News and Insights: This week, Coursera held its annual conference in Las Vegas. A major theme was the shift from knowledge- to skills-based education, which will help many individuals, businesses, and educational institutions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Drone Swarms Go To War, States Ban AI Mental-Health Treatments, Qwen3-Next Accelerates, Transformers Get Energized</title>
      <link>https://www.deeplearning.ai/the-batch/issue-319/</link>
      <description>The Batch AI News and Insights: Automated software testing is growing in importance in the era of AI-assisted coding.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Agents Spend Money, Online Betting Automates, ChatGPT Users Shift, Reinforcement Learning Accelerates</title>
      <link>https://www.deeplearning.ai/the-batch/issue-320/</link>
      <description>The Batch AI News and Insights: Last week, China barred its major tech companies from buying Nvidia chips.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI’s Trillion-Dollar Bet, Generating Viruses, Modeling Planet Earth, Paying for Training Data</title>
      <link>https://www.deeplearning.ai/the-batch/issue-321/</link>
      <description>The Batch AI News and Insights: LandingAI’s Agentic Document Extraction (ADE) turns PDF files into LLM-ready markdown text.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Claude Levels Up, Qwen3 Proliferates, Big AI Diversifies Product Lines, LoRA Adapters on Tap</title>
      <link>https://www.deeplearning.ai/the-batch/issue-322/</link>
      <description>The Batch AI News and Insights: I’m thrilled to announce my latest course: Agentic AI! This course will get you up to speed building cutting-edge agentic workflows.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DeepSeek Cuts Inference Costs, OpenAI Tightens Ties with AMD, Thinking Machines Simplifies Fine-Tuning, Robots Improve Spatial Awareness</title>
      <link>https://www.deeplearning.ai/the-batch/issue-323/</link>
      <description>The Batch AI News and Insights: Readers responded with both surprise and agreement last week when I wrote that the single biggest predictor of how rapidly a team makes progress building an AI agent lay in their ability to drive a disciplined process for evals...</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ling-1T Leads Non-Reasoning Performance, MCP Poses Security Risks, California Regulates AI, Auto-Tune for Agentic Prompts</title>
      <link>https://www.deeplearning.ai/the-batch/issue-324/</link>
      <description>The Batch AI News and Insights: In last week’s letter, I explained how effective agentic AI development needs a disciplined evals and error analysis process, and described an approach to performing evals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monsters of AI: AI Psychosis, Lethal Drones, Decaying Data, Speculative Bubbles</title>
      <link>https://www.deeplearning.ai/the-batch/issue-325/</link>
      <description>The Batch AI News and Insights: Today I’m launching DeepLearning.AI Pro — the one membership that keeps you at the forefront of AI. Please join!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenAI Reorgs For Profit, MiniMax-M2 Leads Open Coding, Universal Music Group Embraces AI, LLMs Go Private</title>
      <link>https://www.deeplearning.ai/the-batch/tag/nov-05-2025/</link>
      <description>The Batch AI News and Insights: AI agents are getting better at looking at different types of data in businesses to spot patterns and create value. This is making data silos increasingly painful.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
