<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>GoogleCloudBlog</title>
    <link>https://cloud.google.com/blog</link>
    <description>Latest posts from https://cloud.google.com/blog. follow.is: feedId:76529357699500032+userId:71370844472670208</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 01:43:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>What’s new with Google Cloud</title>
      <link>https://cloud.google.com/blog/topics/inside-google-cloud/whats-new-google-cloud</link>
      <description>Inside Google CloudWhat’s new with Google CloudBy Google Cloud Content &amp; Editorial  • 25-minute read</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deception in Depth: PRC-Nexus Espionage Campaign Hijacks Web Traffic to Target Diplomats</title>
      <link>https://cloud.google.com/blog/topics/threat-intelligence/prc-nexus-espionage-targets-diplomats</link>
      <description>Threat IntelligenceDeception in Depth: PRC-Nexus Espionage Campaign Hijacks Web Traffic to Target DiplomatsBy Google Threat Intelligence Group  • 19-minute read</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>vLLM Performance Tuning: The Ultimate Guide to xPU Inference Configuration</title>
      <link>https://cloud.google.com/blog/topics/developers-practitioners/vllm-performance-tuning-the-ultimate-guide-to-xpu-inference-configuration</link>
      <description>Developers &amp; PractitionersvLLM Performance Tuning: The Ultimate Guide to xPU Inference ConfigurationBy Eric Hanley • 19-minute read</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chat with your data from anywhere: Announcing Google’s Conversational Analytics API</title>
      <link>https://cloud.google.com/blog/products/data-analytics/understanding-lookers-conversational-analytics-api</link>
      <description>Data AnalyticsChat with your data from anywhere: Announcing Google’s Conversational Analytics APIBy Richard Kuzma • 7-minute read</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing BigQuery geospatial with Earth Engine raster analytics and map visualization</title>
      <link>https://cloud.google.com/blog/products/data-analytics/earth-engine-raster-analytics-and-visualization-in-bigquery-geospatial</link>
      <description>Data AnalyticsEnhancing BigQuery geospatial with Earth Engine raster analytics and map visualizationBy Sheba Rasson • 7-minute read</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Widespread Data Theft Targets Salesforce Instances via Salesloft Drift</title>
      <link>https://cloud.google.com/blog/topics/threat-intelligence/data-theft-salesforce-instances-via-salesloft-drift</link>
      <description>Threat IntelligenceWidespread Data Theft Targets Salesforce Instances via Salesloft DriftBy Google Threat Intelligence Group  • 8-minute read</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building next-gen visuals with Gemini 2.5 Flash Image on Vertex AI</title>
      <link>https://cloud.google.com/blog/products/ai-machine-learning/gemini-2-5-flash-image-on-vertex-ai</link>
      <description>AI &amp; Machine LearningBuilding next-gen visuals with Gemini 2.5 Flash Image on Vertex AIBy Jamie de Guerre • 4-minute read</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Happy birthday, GKE! Let's celebrate with new features and better pricing</title>
      <link>https://cloud.google.com/blog/products/containers-kubernetes/gke-gets-new-pricing-and-capabilities-on-10th-birthday</link>
      <description>Containers &amp; KubernetesHappy birthday, GKE! Let's celebrate with new features and better pricingBy Drew Bradstock • 4-minute read</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Announcing general availability of Firestore with MongoDB compatibility</title>
      <link>https://cloud.google.com/blog/products/databases/firestore-with-mongodb-compatibility-is-now-ga</link>
      <description>DatabasesAnnouncing general availability of Firestore with MongoDB compatibilityBy Minh Nguyen • 4-minute read</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Google named a Leader in IDC MarketScape: Worldwide Incident Response 2025 Vendor Assessment</title>
      <link>https://cloud.google.com/blog/products/identity-security/google-named-a-leader-in-idc-marketscape-worldwide-incident-response-2025-vendor-assessment</link>
      <description>Security &amp; IdentityGoogle named a Leader in IDC MarketScape: Worldwide Incident Response 2025 Vendor AssessmentBy Jurgen Kutscher • 4-minute read</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
