<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>projectdiscovery</title>
    <link>https://projectdiscovery.io/blog</link>
    <description>Latest posts from https://projectdiscovery.io/blog. follow.is: None</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Nov 2025 01:49:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Solving Vulnerability Management: ProjectDiscovery’s RSA Innovation Sandbox Win</title>
      <link>https://projectdiscovery.io/blog/solving-vulnerability-management-projectdiscovery-rsa-innovation-sandbox-win</link>
      <description>Last week, ProjectDiscovery took home the title of Most Innovative Startup at the 2025 RSA Innovation Sandbox, the biggest stage in the world for security innovation. While much of this year’s buzz centered on securing AI, our win was a powerful signal: even as new frontiers emerge, foundational problems like vulnerability management remain unsolved. Security leaders are still spending millions on tools that generate noise instead of insight, and the industry is ready for a better way.

Our COO,</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ProjectDiscovery v1.3: New navigation, dashboard, and improvements</title>
      <link>https://projectdiscovery.io/blog/projectdiscovery-v1-3-new-navigation-dashboard-and-improvements</link>
      <description>We're excited to announce ProjectDiscovery v1.3.0, a significant milestone that transforms how security teams discover, analyze, and respond to vulnerabilities across their attack surface.

These improvements represent months of engineering effort informed by our community's feedback and real-world deployment scenarios. We can’t wait for security teams to get their hands on v1.3.0 and put these new capabilities to work in their own environments.

Redesigned for Speed and Clarity

The new v1.3.0</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Credential Monitoring</title>
      <link>https://projectdiscovery.io/blog/leaked-credential-monitoring</link>
      <description>Imagine discovering that your company's login credentials are sitting in plain sight on the internet, accessible to anyone who knows where to look. Unfortunately, this isn't hypothetical – it's happening right now to organizations worldwide through malware-stolen credentials.


The Hidden Threat: Malware-Stolen Credentials

Every day, cybercriminals deploy malicious software that quietly steals passwords from infected computers. These "stealer" programs harvest credentials from browsers and appl</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with ProjectDiscovery in Linux and Windows</title>
      <link>https://projectdiscovery.io/blog/getting-started-with-projectdiscovery-in-linux-and-windows</link>
      <description>"Just for you, we’ve got this brand new blog all about getting started with ProjectDiscovery on Linux AND Windows."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bug Bounty Etiquette: More than Ethical Hacking (part one)</title>
      <link>https://projectdiscovery.io/blog/bug-bounty-etiquette-more-than-ethical-hacking-part-one</link>
      <description>This is part one of our two-part series on polite hacking, focusing on what to do. Part two talks about what not to do (link coming soon). 

This blog is not about techniques. It’s not about tools to use, how to find the vulnerability, or anything like that. There are plenty of those out there. It’s much more like an etiquette guide for Bug Bounty reporting, and how working within these social norms can lead to better outcomes for you in your career! Think of it like a cotillion class, or the fa</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bug Bounty Etiquette: Our Guide to Polite Hacking (Part Two)</title>
      <link>https://projectdiscovery.io/blog/bug-bounty-etiquette-2-what-not-to-do</link>
      <description>This is the second part of our series on bug bounty etiquette. Part one looks at what you should be doing. 

Last month we talked about bug bounty etiquette and how to be a good bug bounty hunter; not in the sense of finding more bugs, but rather in how to be the kind of bug bounty hunter people want to work with. This time, we have some advice about what NOT to while bug bounty hunting. Let's get started.

 1. Don’t go all out
 2. Don’t ignore the rules
 3. Don’t report unnecessary stuff
 4. Do</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Paddle Strengthened Its Security Posture with ProjectDiscovery</title>
      <link>https://projectdiscovery.io/blog/how-paddle-strengthened-its-security-posture-with-projectdiscovery</link>
      <description>Modern SaaS companies like Paddle face growing security challenges as their platforms expand. To gain full visibility into their attack surface and automate vulnerability detection, Paddle adopted ProjectDiscovery, an open-source security platform that streamlined their security operations.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How ConnectWise streamlined vulnerability detection with ProjectDiscovery</title>
      <link>https://projectdiscovery.io/blog/how-connectwise-streamlined-vulnerability-detection-with-projectdiscovery</link>
      <description>ConnectWise chose ProjectDiscovery over Tenable Cloud to streamline vulnerability detection across 20,000+ AWS instances. By leveraging ProjectDiscovery’s automation and scalability, they achieved efficient, high-volume security monitoring without operational overhead.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Securing the distributed perimeter: How Elastic scaled proactive detection with ProjectDiscovery Cloud</title>
      <link>https://projectdiscovery.io/blog/how-elastic-scaled-proactive-detection-with-projectdiscovery-cloud</link>
      <description>Before going all-in on ProjectDiscovery Cloud, Elastic had already embraced Nuclei, the open-source vulnerability scanner built for customization and speed, along with other ProjectDiscovery tools like naabu and httpx.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Advancing Asset Management - PDCP v0.8.9</title>
      <link>https://projectdiscovery.io/blog/advancing-asset-management-pdcp-v0-8-9-2</link>
      <description>We're excited to announce the release of version 0.8.9 of the ProjectDiscovery Cloud Platform. This update introduces significant enhancements to our asset management capabilities, focusing on asset inventory, AI-powered search, and improved user experience.


Key Features in v0.8.9


Asset Inventory and Technologies

The new interface for cataloging and organizing all assets along with their associated technologies in one place represents a significant advancement in asset management. Now, rega</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Coverage Lie: Why Current Vulnerability Scanners Fail to Stop Breaches</title>
      <link>https://projectdiscovery.io/blog/why-current-vuln-scanners-fail-to-stop-breaches</link>
      <description>First-generation scanners drown teams in noise. Only 6% of CVEs are ever exploited, yet attackers weaponize them in hours. ProjectDiscovery, the RSA Sandbox winner, delivers runtime validation and detections within hours so you can act fast, cut false positives, and close real risk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Detection to Validation: Fixing Broken Vulnerability Workflows</title>
      <link>https://projectdiscovery.io/blog/from-detection-to-validation-fixing-broken-vulnerability-workflows</link>
      <description>By going beyond version checks, you’ll reduce noise, speed up critical fixes, and keep engineering smiling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GCP Cloud Configuration Review Templates - Nuclei Templates v10.2.0 🎉</title>
      <link>https://projectdiscovery.io/blog/gcp-cloud-configuration-review-templates-nuclei-templates-v10-2-0</link>
      <description>We’re excited to tell you about Nuclei Templates release v10.2.0! This new version includes newly added GCP Config Review templates. In this blog post, we’ll discuss automating Google Cloud misconfiguration review, creating custom GCP checks, and sharing results on the PDCP Cloud for review.

Following our last release on Azure Cloud Security Config Review and Kubernetes Cluster Security, we decided to expand our coverage to include GCP as well.

GCP is well-known for its powerful features and v</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nuclei Templates Monthly - May 2025</title>
      <link>https://projectdiscovery.io/blog/nuclei-templates-monthly-may-2025</link>
      <description>Discover the highlights from Nuclei Templates v10.2.1 and v10.2.2 releases: 106 new templates, 57 CVEs covered (including 10 actively exploited KEVs), first-time contributions, a new template bounty program, and key improvements to reduce false positives and negatives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open by design, trusted by enterprises: how we keep Nuclei templates reliable at scale</title>
      <link>https://projectdiscovery.io/blog/open-by-design-trusted-by-enterprises-how-we-keep-nuclei-templates-reliable-at-scale</link>
      <description>At ProjectDiscovery, our greatest strength is our community. Thousands of security researchers, bug bounty hunters, and vulnerability analysts who identify zero‑day vulnerabilities, trending CVEs, and actively exploited vulnerabilities (including those listed in CISA KEV).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-4427/4428 : Ivanti EPMM Remote Code Execution - Technical Analysis</title>
      <link>https://projectdiscovery.io/blog/ivanti-remote-code-execution</link>
      <description>Introduction

As security researchers, we all know that familiar dance when blackbox testing web apps and APIs. You poke an endpoint, get hit with "blah parameter is missing" or "blah is of the wrong type," and after satisfying every requirement, you're often met with the frustrating 401 or 403. That feeling of being so close, yet so far, is something we've all experienced.

However, in a recent analysis of Ivanti EPMM's CVE-2025-4427 and CVE-2025-4428 , this very flow of execution – validation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Authentication Bypass to RCE in Versa Concerto</title>
      <link>https://projectdiscovery.io/blog/versa-concerto-authentication-bypass-rce</link>
      <description>Introduction

Versa Concerto is a widely used network security and SD-WAN orchestration platform, designed to provide seamless policy management, analytics, and automation for enterprises. With a growing customer base that includes large enterprises, service providers, and government entities, the security of this platform is critical. Given its extensive adoption and potential exposure to external threats, we initiated research to assess its security posture and uncover possible vulnerabilities</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Code Execution in DELMIA Apriso</title>
      <link>https://projectdiscovery.io/blog/remote-code-execution-in-delmia-apriso</link>
      <description>Introduction

DELMIA Apriso is a manufacturing execution and operations orchestration platform used by large manufacturers, service providers, and critical infrastructure operators. Because the product exposes multiple integration points (SOAP, file uploads, provisioning feeds) that are often reachable from internal networks, we performed a focused black-box assessment to surface integration and surface-area weaknesses.

Our testing uncovered two chained, high-impact issues: an unauthenticated S</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Remote Code Execution in DELMIA Apriso</title>
      <link>https://projectdiscovery.io/blog/remote-code-execution-in-delmia-apriso</link>
      <description>Introduction

DELMIA Apriso is a manufacturing execution and operations orchestration platform used by large manufacturers, service providers, and critical infrastructure operators. Because the product exposes multiple integration points (SOAP, file uploads, provisioning feeds) that are often reachable from internal networks, we performed a focused black-box assessment to surface integration and surface-area weaknesses.

Our testing uncovered two chained, high-impact issues: an unauthenticated S</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Detection to Validation: Fixing Broken Vulnerability Workflows</title>
      <link>https://projectdiscovery.io/blog/from-detection-to-validation-fixing-broken-vulnerability-workflows</link>
      <description>By going beyond version checks, you’ll reduce noise, speed up critical fixes, and keep engineering smiling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Open by design, trusted by enterprises: how we keep Nuclei templates reliable at scale</title>
      <link>https://projectdiscovery.io/blog/open-by-design-trusted-by-enterprises-how-we-keep-nuclei-templates-reliable-at-scale</link>
      <description>At ProjectDiscovery, our greatest strength is our community. Thousands of security researchers, bug bounty hunters, and vulnerability analysts who identify zero‑day vulnerabilities, trending CVEs, and actively exploited vulnerabilities (including those listed in CISA KEV).</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
