<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>rapid7_blog</title>
    <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/posts/</link>
    <description>Latest posts from https://www.rapid7.com/blog/posts/. follow.is: feedId:71371191432910863+userId:71370844472670208</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 May 2025 01:46:36 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Metasploit Wrap-Up 04/18/2025</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/18/metasploit-wrap-up-04-18-2025/</link>
      <description>Smaller Fetch Payloads
This week, a significant enhancement was made to the already awesome fetch
payload
 
feature by our very own bwatters-r7 . The
improvement introduces a new option, PIPE_FETCH, which optimizes the process by
serving both the payload and the command to be executed simultaneously.

This enhancement directly addresses the challenge of limited s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Lessons from Take Command 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/21/top-lessons-from-take-command-2025/</link>
      <description>Take Command 2025 delivered big insights on AI, exposure management, red teaming, and cloud defense. Catch up with on-demand sessions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Noise to Action: Introducing Intelligence Hub</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/23/from-noise-to-action-introducing-intelligence-hub/</link>
      <description>We are delighted to announce the availability of Intelligence Hub, an evolution in threat intelligence delivery that is designed to provide meaningful context and actionable insights integrated with the Rapid7 Command Platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE NEW Rapid7 MDR for Enterprise: Tailored Detection and Response for Complex Environments</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/24/the-new-rapid7-mdr-for-enterprise-tailored-detection-and-response-for-complex-environments/</link>
      <description>We’re excited to introduce Rapid7 MDR for Enterprise—a fully managed, customized detection and response service designed to meet the complexity of the modern enterprise head-on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metasploit Wrap-Up 04/25/2025</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/25/metasploit-wrap-up-04-25-2025/</link>
      <description>AD CS workflow improvement with new PKCS12 features
Given the increasing popularity of AD CS misconfiguration exploitation in recent
years, Metasploit has been consistently improving its capabilities in this area.
This week’s release introduces a new certs command to the msfconsole, enabling
users to manage PKCS12 certificates stored in the database, similar to the klist 
 command</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Active exploitation of SAP NetWeaver Visual Composer CVE-2025-31324</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/28/etr-active-exploitation-of-sap-netweaver-visual-composer-cve-2025-31324/</link>
      <description>A critical SAP NetWeaver zero-day vulnerability (CVE-2025-31324) that allows for full SAP server compromise is being actively exploited in the wild.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Rapid7’s Exposure Assessment Platform Buyer’s Guide</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/28/introducing-rapid7s-exposure-assessment-platform-buyers-guide/</link>
      <description>To help organizations navigate this rapidly changing threat landscape, we are excited to introduce the Exposure Assessment Platform (EAP) Buyer’s Guide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Exposure to Assurance: Unified Remediation Across the Security Lifecycle</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/29/from-exposure-to-assurance-unified-remediation-across-the-security-lifecycle/</link>
      <description>Rapid7’s Exposure Command directly addresses this gap, combining advanced risk-based vulnerability management (RBVM) with environmental context, threat intelligence, and native workflow automation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driving down MTTR with Remediation Hub, Available in Rapid7 Exposure Command</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/29/driving-down-mttr-with-remediation-hub-available-in-rapid7-exposure-command/</link>
      <description>Rapid7’s Remediation Hub enables security teams to go beyond simply identifying vulnerabilities and focus more on remediating risk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deepening the MDR partnership: Rapid7 now delivers Active Remediation with Velociraptor</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/29/deepening-the-mdr-partnership-rapid7-now-delivers-active-remediation-with-velociraptor/</link>
      <description>Powered by our best-in-class, open-source digital forensics and incident response (DFIR) tool, Rapid7 MDR analysts can take direct, approved remediation actions on your behalf.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InsightIDR AI Alert Triage Automatically Classifies Alerts with 99.93% Accuracy</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/29/insightidr-ai-alert-triage-automatically-classifies-alerts-with-99-93-accuracy/</link>
      <description>Rapid7's AI Alert Triage –  trained and tested by the Rapid7 global MDR service across trillions of alerts worldwide — will soon be available to users of our next-gen SIEM, InsightIDR, at no additional cost.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reinforcing resilience with financial assurance: Breach protection matters now more than ever</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/29/reinforcing-resilience-with-financial-assurance-breach-protection-matters-now-more-than-ever/</link>
      <description>Introducing Rapid7’s value-added Breach Protection Warranty that delivers confidence, clarity, and coverage when it matters most.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three Takeaways from the Gartner® Report: How to Grow Vulnerability Management Into Exposure Management</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/30/three-takeaways-from-the-gartner-r-report-how-to-grow-vulnerability-management-into-exposure-management/</link>
      <description>Latest research from Gartner, How to Grow Vulnerability Management Into Exposure Management, highlights the need for security teams to move beyond simply tracking vulnerabilities and embrace a more comprehensive approach to exposure management.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI and Resilience Take the Spotlight in 2025: Key Trends from Gartner® Cybersecurity Research</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/05/01/ai-and-resilience-take-the-spotlight-in-2025-key-trends-from-gartner-r-cybersecurity-research/</link>
      <description>Here are three trends that stand out for leaders aiming to build a more resilient, AI-ready security program in 2025.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why is Ransomware Still a Thing in 2025?</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/05/01/why-is-ransomware-still-a-thing-in-2025/</link>
      <description>Ransomware remains a crisis because we are still giving attackers the upper hand. To regain control, we need to understand how we’ve made it so easy for them, and what we can do to change that.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
