<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>rapid7_blog</title>
    <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/posts/</link>
    <description>Latest posts from https://www.rapid7.com/blog/posts/. follow.is: feedId:71371191432910863+userId:71370844472670208</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2025 01:47:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanti Connect Secure CVE-2025-22457 exploited in the wild</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/03/etr-ivanti-connect-secure-cve-2025-22457-exploited-in-the-wild/</link>
      <description>On April 3, 2025, Ivanti disclosed CVE-2025-22457, a critical a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability that allows for remote code execution on affected devices.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pentales: Red Team vs. N-Day (and How We Won)</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/04/pentales-red-team-vs-n-day-and-how-we-won/</link>
      <description>While the organization involved remains anonymous, the events described are real. This story reflects how our always-on testing approach closely mirrors the creativity and persistence of actual threat actors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metasploit Wrap-Up 04/04/2025</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/04/metasploit-wrap-up-04-04-2025/</link>
      <description>New RCEs
Metasploit added four new modules this week, including three that leverage
vulnerabilities to obtain remote code execution (RCE)
. Among
these three, two leverage deserialization, showing that the exploit primitive is
still going strong. The Tomcat vulnerability in particular CVE-2025-24813
 garnered a lot of
attention when it was disclosed; however, to f</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don’t Miss Out: What You Need to Know Before Take Command 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/07/dont-miss-out-what-you-need-to-know-before-take-command-2025/</link>
      <description>Join Rapid7’s Take Command 2025 on April 9 for expert insights into ransomware, threat trends, and live discussions with top security leaders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2025 Ransomware: Business as Usual, Business is Booming</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/08/2025-ransomware-business-as-usual-business-is-booming/</link>
      <description>Rapid7 Labs took a look at internal and publicly-available ransomware data for Q1 2025 and added our own insights to provide a picture of the year thus far—and what you can do now to reduce your attack surface against ransomware.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patch Tuesday - April 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/08/patch-tuesday-april-2025/</link>
      <description>CLFS zero-day. LDAP critical RCEs. RDS critical RCEs. Hyper-V critical RCE.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Password Spray Attacks Taking Advantage of Lax MFA</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/10/password-spray-attacks-taking-advantage-of-lax-mfa/</link>
      <description>In the first quarter of 2025, Rapid7’s Managed Threat Hunting team observed a significant volume of brute-force password attempts leveraging FastHTTP, a high-performance HTTP server and client library for Go, to automate unauthorized logins via HTTP requests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metasploit Weekly Wrap-Up 04/11/2025</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/11/metasploit-weekly-wrap-up-04-11-2025/</link>
      <description>Spring Exploits
This weekly release of Metasploit Framework includes new RCE exploit modules for
several vulnerable applications: Appsmith, a low-code application platform which
contains a misconfiguration on PostgreSQL (CVE-2024-55964); Pandora FMS, a
monitoring solution, where, once gained access to the administrator panel is
possible to inject commands (CVE-2024-12971); Oracle Access Manager, a SSO
application containing an unauthenticated deserialization vulnerability
(CVE-2021-35587); and p</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Take Command 2025: A Day of Insight, Innovation, and Impact</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/14/take-command-2025-a-day-of-insight-innovation-and-impact/</link>
      <description>Explore top insights from Take Command 2025—ransomware, AI, red teaming, and more. All sessions now available on demand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Following the News: MITRE’s Common Vulnerabilities and Exposures (CVE) Funding</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/16/following-the-news-mitres-common-vulnerabilities-and-exposures-cve-funding/</link>
      <description>Rapid7 continues to monitor both public and private discussions closely in its capacity as a CVE Numbering Authority (CNA) and as a longtime leader and participant in the CVE ecosystem.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metasploit Wrap-Up 04/18/2025</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/18/metasploit-wrap-up-04-18-2025/</link>
      <description>Smaller Fetch Payloads
This week, a significant enhancement was made to the already awesome fetch
payload
 
feature by our very own bwatters-r7 . The
improvement introduces a new option, PIPE_FETCH, which optimizes the process by
serving both the payload and the command to be executed simultaneously.

This enhancement directly addresses the challenge of limited s</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Top Lessons from Take Command 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/21/top-lessons-from-take-command-2025/</link>
      <description>Take Command 2025 delivered big insights on AI, exposure management, red teaming, and cloud defense. Catch up with on-demand sessions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Noise to Action: Introducing Intelligence Hub</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/23/from-noise-to-action-introducing-intelligence-hub/</link>
      <description>We are delighted to announce the availability of Intelligence Hub, an evolution in threat intelligence delivery that is designed to provide meaningful context and actionable insights integrated with the Rapid7 Command Platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>THE NEW Rapid7 MDR for Enterprise: Tailored Detection and Response for Complex Environments</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/24/the-new-rapid7-mdr-for-enterprise-tailored-detection-and-response-for-complex-environments/</link>
      <description>We’re excited to introduce Rapid7 MDR for Enterprise—a fully managed, customized detection and response service designed to meet the complexity of the modern enterprise head-on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metasploit Wrap-Up 04/25/2025</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/25/metasploit-wrap-up-04-25-2025/</link>
      <description>AD CS workflow improvement with new PKCS12 features
Given the increasing popularity of AD CS misconfiguration exploitation in recent
years, Metasploit has been consistently improving its capabilities in this area.
This week’s release introduces a new certs command to the msfconsole, enabling
users to manage PKCS12 certificates stored in the database, similar to the klist 
 command</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
