<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>rapid7_blog</title>
    <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/posts/</link>
    <description>Latest posts from https://www.rapid7.com/blog/posts/. follow.is: feedId:71371191432910863+userId:71370844472670208</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 01:41:31 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Rapid7 MDR Supports AWS GuardDuty's New Attack Sequence Alerts</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/03/21/rapid7-mdr-supports-aws-guarddutys-new-attack-sequence-alerts/</link>
      <description>AWS GuardDuty has introduced two powerful new alerts that enhance its threat detection capabilities: "Potential Credential Compromise" and "Potential S3 Data Compromise."</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metasploit Wrap-Up 03/21/2025</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/03/21/metasploit-wrap-up-03-21-2025/</link>
      <description>SMB to LDAP Relay
This week, the Metasploit team have added an exciting relay module that has been
in the works for a long time. This relay module is used to host an SMB server,
and execute an SMB to LDAP relay attack against a Domain controller with an LDAP
server when NTLMv1 is being used as the SMB authentication method. PetitPotam
can be used to coerce authentication on the victim system and relay it to the
Domain Controller.The module automatically takes care of removing the relevant
flags</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notable vulnerabilities in Next.js (CVE-2025-29927) and CrushFTP</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/03/25/etr-notable-vulnerabilities-in-next-js-cve-2025-29927/</link>
      <description>Rapid7 is warning customers of two notable vulnerabilities affecting Next.js (CVE-2025-29927) and file transfer software CrushFTP (no CVE).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple vulnerabilities in Ingress NGINX Controller for Kubernetes</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/03/25/etr-multiple-vulnerabilities-in-ingress-nginx-controller-for-kubernetes/</link>
      <description>On March 24, 2025, Kubernetes disclosed 5 new vulnerabilities affecting the Ingress NGINX Controller for Kubernetes. Successful exploitation could allow attackers access to all secrets stored across all namespaces in the Kubernetes cluster, which could result in cluster takeover.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Inside the Mind of the Attacker: A Conversation with Raj Samani</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/03/26/inside-the-mind-of-the-attacker-a-conversation-with-raj-samani/</link>
      <description>Join Take Command 2025, a free virtual cybersecurity event on April 9. Hear from industry experts on AI-driven security, real-world attack simulations, and frontline SOC threat hunting strategies. Register now!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapid7 Earns 5-Star Rating in the 2025 CRN® Partner Program Guide</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/03/26/rapid7-earns-5-star-rating-in-the-2025-crn-r-partner-program-guide/</link>
      <description>Rapid7 has been honored by CRN®, a brand of The Channel Company, with a 5-Star Award in the 2025 CRN Partner Program Guide. This annual guide is an essential resource for solution providers seeking vendor partner programs that match their business goals and deliver high partner value.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unpacking a post-compromise breach simulation with Vector Command</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/03/27/unpacking-a-post-compromise-breach-simulation-with-vector-command/</link>
      <description>This blog is the third in our Vector Command series, where we explore the tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs) leveraged by Rapid7’s expert red team.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Overcoming the Challenges of Vulnerability Remediation</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/03/28/overcoming-the-challenges-of-vulnerability-remediation/</link>
      <description>The following is a guest blog post by Zac Youtz, Co-Founder and CTO at valued Rapid7 partner, Furl. Here, Zac discusses how to effectively remediate vulnerabilities discovered by Rapid7’s InsightVM.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metasploit Wrap-Up 03/28/2025</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/03/28/metasploit-wrap-up-03-28-2025/</link>
      <description>Windows LPE - Cloud File Mini Filer Driver Heap Overflow
This Metasploit release includes an exploit module for CVE-2024-30085, an LPE in
cldflt.sys which is known as the Windows Cloud Files Mini Filer Driver. This
driver allows users to manage and sync files between a remote server and a local
client. The exploit module allows users with an existing session on an affected
Windows device to seamlessly escalate their privileges to NT AUTHORITY\SYSTEM.
This module has been tested on Windows workst</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seeing is Securing: MDR VALUE at-a-glance with the Detection and Response Dashboard</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/03/31/seeing-is-securing-mdr-value-at-a-glance-with-the-detection-response-dashboard/</link>
      <description>The Detection &amp; Response Dashboard provides a clear, high-level snapshot of your entire MDR program. The customizable and downloadable summary visualizes key metrics, helping teams quickly identify risks, trends, and security outcomes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What’s New in Rapid7 Products &amp; Services: Q1 2025 in Review</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/01/whats-new-in-rapid7-products-services-q1-2025-in-review/</link>
      <description>Read on for Q1 2025 release highlights across the Command Platform, from Exposure Command to Managed Threat Complete.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A New Approach to Managing Vulnerabilities is Required - Work Smarter not Harder with Rapid7 Remediation Hub</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/01/a-new-approach-to-managing-vulnerabilities-is-required-work-smarter-not-harder-with-rapid7-remediation-hub/</link>
      <description>Rapid7’s Remediation Hub takes a remediation-based view rather than an individual CVE based view of vulnerability management. It shows security teams the volume of vulnerabilities that will be resolved by carrying out a recommended remediation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Rebirth of a Cursed Existence? Examining ‘Babuk Locker 2.0’ Ransomware</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/02/a-rebirth-of-a-cursed-existence-the-babuk-locker-2-0/</link>
      <description>In early 2025, we came across a channel promoting itself as Babuk Locker. Since the original group had shut down in 2021, we decided to investigate whether this was a rebrand or a new threat.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Preview the Action: Two New Sessions Available Before Take Command 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/02/preview-the-action-two-new-sessions-available-before-take-command-2025/</link>
      <description>Join Take Command 2025, a free virtual cybersecurity event on April 9. Hear from industry experts on AI-driven security, real-world attack simulations, and frontline SOC threat hunting strategies. Register now!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanti Connect Secure CVE-2025-22457 exploited in the wild</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/03/etr-ivanti-connect-secure-cve-2025-22457-exploited-in-the-wild/</link>
      <description>On April 3, 2025, Ivanti disclosed CVE-2025-22457, a critical a stack-based buffer overflow vulnerability that allows for remote code execution on affected devices.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
