<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>rapid7_blog</title>
    <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/posts/</link>
    <description>Latest posts from https://www.rapid7.com/blog/posts/. follow.is: feedId:71371191432910863+userId:71370844472670208</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 01:52:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Threats don’t wait, neither should you: Mastering Emergent Threat Response Validation</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/05/23/mastering-emergent-threat-response-validation/</link>
      <description>Rapid7 Labs uncovers emerging threats and delivers cutting-edge research; Vector Command puts that intelligence to work—validating response strategies, optimizing defenses, and ensuring organizations are ready when it matters most. Because in cybersecurity, the best defense is a well-prepared team.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retail Under Siege: What Recent Cyber Attacks Tell Us About Today’s Threat Landscape</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/05/27/retail-under-siege-what-recent-cyber-attacks-tell-us-about-todays-threat-landscape/</link>
      <description>When several major UK organizations, including well-known retail brands, found themselves caught in a cyber attack earlier this year, it made headlines – reflecting a growing trend where attackers exploit third-party vendors to breach businesses through a single point of entry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key Takeaways from the Take Command Summit 2025: Customer Panel on Future-Proofing VM Programs</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/05/28/key-takeaways-from-the-take-command-summit-2025-customer-panel-on-future-proofing-vm-programs/</link>
      <description>Learn how security leaders are evolving VM into exposure management. Get key takeaways from the Take Command 2025 customer panel. Watch on demand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-48045, CVE-2025-48046, CVE-2025-48047: MICI NetFax Server Product Vulnerabilities (NOT FIXED)</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/05/29/cve-2025-48045-cve-2025-48046-cve-2025-48047-mici-netfax-server-product-vulnerabilities-not-fixed/</link>
      <description>Over a penetration testing engagement, Rapid7 discovered 3 vulnerabilities in MICI Network Co., Ltd’s NetFax server allowing for an authenticated attack chain resulting in Remote Code Execution (RCE) against the device as the root user.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seeing Is Securing: How Surface Command Expands MDR Visibility and Impact</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/05/30/seeing-is-securing-how-surface-command-expands-mdr-visibility-and-impact/</link>
      <description>To maximize the effectiveness of security operations, MDR must continually evolve. Today at Rapid7, that means integrating Surface Command — not as a dashboard or tool to manage, but as a behind-the-scenes capability that strengthens the service our customers rely on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metasploit Wrap-Up 05/30/2025</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/05/30/metasploit-wrap-up-05-30-2025/</link>
      <description>The internet is a series of Tube 
Metasploit has supported SOCKS proxies for years now, being able to both act as
both a client (by setting the Proxies datastore option) and a server (by running
the auxiliary/server/socks_proxy module). While Metasploit has supported both
SOCKS versions 4a and 5, there became some ambiguity in regards to how Domain
Name System (DNS) requests are made by Metasploit through these versions. Both
versions 4a and 5 notably enable clients to make connections to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key Takeaways from the Take Command Summit 2025: Risk Revolution – Proactive Strategies for Exposure Management</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/06/02/key-takeaways-from-the-take-command-summit-2025-risk-revolution-proactive-strategies-for-exposure-management/</link>
      <description>Learn how security teams are evolving risk strategies with exposure management. Hear insights from Rapid7 and ESG. Watch the full session on demand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing AI Attack Coverage in Exposure Command: Secure what traditional AppSec Tools miss</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/06/03/introducing-ai-attack-coverage-in-exposure-command-secure-what-traditional-appsec-tools-miss/</link>
      <description>Introducing AI Attack Coverage in Exposure Command and InsightAppSec, bringing purpose built protection for AI driven applications into your existing AppSec workflows. Uncover vulnerabilities that legacy tools miss – and stop AI specific threats before they become business problems.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Ideology to Financial Gain: Exploring the Convergence from Hacktivism to Cybercrime</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/06/03/from-ideology-to-financial-gain-exploring-the-convergence-from-hacktivism-to-cybercrime/</link>
      <description>The lines between ideologically-driven hacktivism and financially motivated cybercriminals are blurring. Some hacktivist groups are evolving into ransomware operations – even becoming ransomware affiliates – merging the disruptive zeal of hacktivism with the ruthless efficiency of cybercrime.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rapid7 Q1 2025 Incident Response Findings</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/06/04/rapid7-q1-2025-incident-response-findings/</link>
      <description>Rapid7’s 2025Q1 incident response data highlights several key IAV trends, shares salient examples of incidents investigated by the Rapid7 IR team, and digs into threat data by industry as well as some of the more commonly seen pieces of malware.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India's Cyber Leaders Prepare for AI-Driven Threats</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/06/06/indias-cyber-leaders-prepare-for-ai-driven-threats/</link>
      <description>As India's economy rapidly digitizes, cybersecurity challenges are becoming increasingly complex. This May, Rapid7 launched our inaugural Global Security Day series across India, bringing together top security leaders to address the most pressing cyber threats facing organizations in 2025.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cultivating Growth and Development at Rapid7</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/06/06/cultivating-growth-and-development-at-rapid7/</link>
      <description>At Rapid7, we’re pushing the boundaries on what a cybersecurity company can be. With more than a dozen offices around the world, Rapid7’s culture provides a foundation where people can grow their skills and progress in their careers, while driving meaningful impact to the business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metasploit Wrap-up 06/06/25</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/06/06/metasploit-wrapup-76/</link>
      <description>This release adds new modules targeting ThinManager vulnerabilities (CVE-2023-27855, CVE-2023-2917, CVE-2023-27856), a udev persistence module for Linux, an Ivanti EPMM authentication bypass and remote code execution module (CVE-2025-4427, CVE-2025-4428), PHP payload adapters, and more</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navigating AWS Migration: Achieving Clarity and Confidence</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/06/09/navigating-aws-migration-achieving-clarity-and-confidence-2/</link>
      <description>Migrating workloads to Amazon Web Services (AWS) represents a significant strategic opportunity, enabling greater agility, scalability, and potential for innovation. But undertaking this transition without a comprehensive strategy introduce unforeseen risks, operational delays, and more.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5 Things Security Leaders Need to Know About Agentic AI</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/06/09/5-things-security-leaders-need-to-know-about-agentic-ai/</link>
      <description>Generative AI has already transformed the way businesses work. But we’re now entering a new phase where AI doesn’t just generate content, but takes independent action on our behalf. This next evolution is called ‘agentic AI’, and it’s moving fast.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
