<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>rapid7_blog</title>
    <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/posts/</link>
    <description>Latest posts from https://www.rapid7.com/blog/posts/. follow.is: feedId:71371191432910863+userId:71370844472670208</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 01:51:10 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Patch Tuesday - May 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/05/13/patch-tuesday-may-2025/</link>
      <description>Seven zero-days: Window Scripting Engine, 2x CLFS, DWM, Visual Studio, AFD for Winsock, Defender for Identity.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-32756 Exploited in the Wild, Affecting Multiple Fortinet Products</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/05/14/etr-multiple-fortinet-products-cve-2025-32756-exploited-in-the-wild/</link>
      <description>On May 13, 2025, Fortinet disclosed CVE-2025-32756, an unauthenticated stack-based buffer overflow affecting multiple FortiNet products; including FortiVoice, FortiRecorder, FortiNDR, FortiMail, and FortiCamera.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ivanti Endpoint Manager Mobile exploit chain exploited in the wild</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/05/16/etr-ivanti-epmm-exploit-chain-exploited-in-the-wild/</link>
      <description>On May 13, 2025, Ivanti disclosed an exploited in the wild exploit chain, comprising of two new vulnerabilities affecting Ivanti Endpoint Manager Mobile: CVE-2025-4427 and CVE-2025-4428.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metasploit Wrap-Up 05/16/2025</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/05/16/metasploit-wrap-up-05-16-2025/</link>
      <description>New modules for everyone
This week’s release is packed with new module content. We have RCE modules for
Car Rental System 1.0, Wordpress plugins SureTriggers, User Registration and
Membership. We also have a persistence module for LINQPad software and an
auxiliary module for POWERCOM UPSMON PRO. We have also added support for 32-bit
architectures to our execute-assembly post module, which now supports injection
of both 64-bit and 32-bit .NET assembly binaries.

New module content (5)
POWERCOM UP</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key Takeaways from the Take Command Summit 2025: Inside the Mind of an Attacker</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/05/21/key-takeaways-from-the-take-command-summit-2025-inside-the-mind-of-an-attacker/</link>
      <description>In one of the most anticipated sessions of Take Command 2025, Raj Samani, Chief Scientist at Rapid7, sat down with Trent Teyema, former FBI Special Agent and President of CSG Strategies, for a candid conversation on how threat actors are evolving and what defenders must do to keep up.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NSIS Abuse and sRDI Shellcode: Anatomy of the Winos 4.0 Campaign</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/05/22/nsis-abuse-and-srdi-shellcode-anatomy-of-the-winos-4-0-campaign/</link>
      <description>Rapid7 has been tracking a malware campaign that uses fake software installers disguised as popular apps like VPN and QQBrowser—to deliver Winos v4.0, a hard-to-detect malware that runs entirely in memory and gives attackers remote access.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What the Take Command 2025 Survey Tells Us About the State of Security</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/05/22/what-the-take-command-2025-survey-tells-us-about-the-state-of-security/</link>
      <description>After the Take Command 2025 Virtual Cybersecurity Summit sessions wrapped, we surveyed attendees to understand where their security programs stand today, what challenges they’re facing, and what they found most valuable during the event.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metasploit Wrap-Up</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/05/22/metasploit-wrap-up-157/</link>
      <description>Making Metasploit faster
This week's wrap-up includes many new modules, but notably, we've upgraded
Metasploit loading. Thanks to bcoles , the bootup
performance when searching for a module has been increased in #20166
. Also, we've reduced
Metasploit startup time - in #20155
.

New module content (6)
Gather Ticket Granting Service (TGS) tickets for Use</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Threats don’t wait, neither should you: Mastering Emergent Threat Response Validation</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/05/23/mastering-emergent-threat-response-validation/</link>
      <description>Rapid7 Labs uncovers emerging threats and delivers cutting-edge research; Vector Command puts that intelligence to work—validating response strategies, optimizing defenses, and ensuring organizations are ready when it matters most. Because in cybersecurity, the best defense is a well-prepared team.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Retail Under Siege: What Recent Cyber Attacks Tell Us About Today’s Threat Landscape</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/05/27/retail-under-siege-what-recent-cyber-attacks-tell-us-about-todays-threat-landscape/</link>
      <description>When several major UK organizations, including well-known retail brands, found themselves caught in a cyber attack earlier this year, it made headlines – reflecting a growing trend where attackers exploit third-party vendors to breach businesses through a single point of entry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key Takeaways from the Take Command Summit 2025: Customer Panel on Future-Proofing VM Programs</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/05/28/key-takeaways-from-the-take-command-summit-2025-customer-panel-on-future-proofing-vm-programs/</link>
      <description>Learn how security leaders are evolving VM into exposure management. Get key takeaways from the Take Command 2025 customer panel. Watch on demand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CVE-2025-48045, CVE-2025-48046, CVE-2025-48047: MICI NetFax Server Product Vulnerabilities (NOT FIXED)</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/05/29/cve-2025-48045-cve-2025-48046-cve-2025-48047-mici-netfax-server-product-vulnerabilities-not-fixed/</link>
      <description>Over a penetration testing engagement, Rapid7 discovered 3 vulnerabilities in MICI Network Co., Ltd’s NetFax server allowing for an authenticated attack chain resulting in Remote Code Execution (RCE) against the device as the root user.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seeing Is Securing: How Surface Command Expands MDR Visibility and Impact</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/05/30/seeing-is-securing-how-surface-command-expands-mdr-visibility-and-impact/</link>
      <description>To maximize the effectiveness of security operations, MDR must continually evolve. Today at Rapid7, that means integrating Surface Command — not as a dashboard or tool to manage, but as a behind-the-scenes capability that strengthens the service our customers rely on.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metasploit Wrap-Up 05/30/2025</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/05/30/metasploit-wrap-up-05-30-2025/</link>
      <description>The internet is a series of Tube 
Metasploit has supported SOCKS proxies for years now, being able to both act as
both a client (by setting the Proxies datastore option) and a server (by running
the auxiliary/server/socks_proxy module). While Metasploit has supported both
SOCKS versions 4a and 5, there became some ambiguity in regards to how Domain
Name System (DNS) requests are made by Metasploit through these versions. Both
versions 4a and 5 notably enable clients to make connections to</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key Takeaways from the Take Command Summit 2025: Risk Revolution – Proactive Strategies for Exposure Management</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/06/02/key-takeaways-from-the-take-command-summit-2025-risk-revolution-proactive-strategies-for-exposure-management/</link>
      <description>Learn how security teams are evolving risk strategies with exposure management. Hear insights from Rapid7 and ESG. Watch the full session on demand.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
