<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>rapid7_blog</title>
    <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/posts/</link>
    <description>Latest posts from https://www.rapid7.com/blog/posts/. follow.is: feedId:71371191432910863+userId:71370844472670208</description>
    <docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs>
    <generator>python-feedgen</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 May 2025 01:51:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <item>
      <title>Active exploitation of SAP NetWeaver Visual Composer CVE-2025-31324</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/28/etr-active-exploitation-of-sap-netweaver-visual-composer-cve-2025-31324/</link>
      <description>A critical SAP NetWeaver zero-day vulnerability (CVE-2025-31324) that allows for full SAP server compromise is being actively exploited in the wild.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introducing Rapid7’s Exposure Assessment Platform Buyer’s Guide</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/28/introducing-rapid7s-exposure-assessment-platform-buyers-guide/</link>
      <description>To help organizations navigate this rapidly changing threat landscape, we are excited to introduce the Exposure Assessment Platform (EAP) Buyer’s Guide.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Exposure to Assurance: Unified Remediation Across the Security Lifecycle</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/29/from-exposure-to-assurance-unified-remediation-across-the-security-lifecycle/</link>
      <description>Rapid7’s Exposure Command directly addresses this gap, combining advanced risk-based vulnerability management (RBVM) with environmental context, threat intelligence, and native workflow automation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Driving down MTTR with Remediation Hub, Available in Rapid7 Exposure Command</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/29/driving-down-mttr-with-remediation-hub-available-in-rapid7-exposure-command/</link>
      <description>Rapid7’s Remediation Hub enables security teams to go beyond simply identifying vulnerabilities and focus more on remediating risk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Deepening the MDR partnership: Rapid7 now delivers Active Remediation with Velociraptor</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/29/deepening-the-mdr-partnership-rapid7-now-delivers-active-remediation-with-velociraptor/</link>
      <description>Powered by our best-in-class, open-source digital forensics and incident response (DFIR) tool, Rapid7 MDR analysts can take direct, approved remediation actions on your behalf.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>InsightIDR AI Alert Triage Automatically Classifies Alerts with 99.93% Accuracy</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/29/insightidr-ai-alert-triage-automatically-classifies-alerts-with-99-93-accuracy/</link>
      <description>Rapid7's AI Alert Triage –  trained and tested by the Rapid7 global MDR service across trillions of alerts worldwide — will soon be available to users of our next-gen SIEM, InsightIDR, at no additional cost.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reinforcing resilience with financial assurance: Breach protection matters now more than ever</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/29/reinforcing-resilience-with-financial-assurance-breach-protection-matters-now-more-than-ever/</link>
      <description>Introducing Rapid7’s value-added Breach Protection Warranty that delivers confidence, clarity, and coverage when it matters most.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three Takeaways from the Gartner® Report: How to Grow Vulnerability Management Into Exposure Management</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/04/30/three-takeaways-from-the-gartner-r-report-how-to-grow-vulnerability-management-into-exposure-management/</link>
      <description>Latest research from Gartner, How to Grow Vulnerability Management Into Exposure Management, highlights the need for security teams to move beyond simply tracking vulnerabilities and embrace a more comprehensive approach to exposure management.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI and Resilience Take the Spotlight in 2025: Key Trends from Gartner® Cybersecurity Research</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/05/01/ai-and-resilience-take-the-spotlight-in-2025-key-trends-from-gartner-r-cybersecurity-research/</link>
      <description>Here are three trends that stand out for leaders aiming to build a more resilient, AI-ready security program in 2025.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why is Ransomware Still a Thing in 2025?</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/05/01/why-is-ransomware-still-a-thing-in-2025/</link>
      <description>Ransomware remains a crisis because we are still giving attackers the upper hand. To regain control, we need to understand how we’ve made it so easy for them, and what we can do to change that.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metasploit Wrap-Up 05/02/2025</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/05/02/metasploit-wrap-up-114/</link>
      <description>Meterpreter Extended API Clipboard Monitoring
Security is hard, and Open Source Security is a collaborative effort. This week,
Metasploit released a fix for a vulnerability that was privately disclosed to us
by long-time community member bcoles . The
vulnerability in question impacted Metasploit users who were using the clipboard
monitoring functionality contained within the extended-API Meterpreter extension
(extapi). After a user enables monitoring, they would typica</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Key Takeaways from the Take Command Summit 2025: From Zero to Hero: Building the Perfect Defense</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/05/06/key-takeaways-from-the-take-command-summit-2025-from-zero-to-hero-building-the-perfect-defense/</link>
      <description>Discover key lessons from Take Command 2025 on building proactive, resilient cybersecurity defenses. Watch Ted Harrington’s full session on demand.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Exploring an Untethered, Unified Approach to CTEM</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/05/07/exploring-an-untethered-unified-approach-to-ctem/</link>
      <description>Unlike traditional standalone VM, CASM, EASM, SIEM, or EDR tools that rely on proprietary agents, Exposure Command from Rapid7 brings it all together into one platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Multiple vulnerabilities in SonicWall SMA 100 series (FIXED)</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/05/07/multiple-vulnerabilities-in-sonicwall-sma-100-series-2025/</link>
      <description>Rapid7 is disclosing three new vulnerabilities in SonicWall SMA 100 series appliances (CVE-2025-32819, CVE-2025-32820, and CVE-2025-32821). An attacker with access to an SMA SSLVPN user account can chain these vulnerabilities for root-level code execution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Metasploit Wrap-Up 05/09/2025</title>
      <link>https://www.rapid7.com/blog/post/2025/05/09/metasploit-wrap-up-05-09-2025/</link>
      <description>New Toys and New Techniques
This release features a new OPNSense login scanner, a module targeting the Sante
PACS path traversal vulnerability, an additional method for stealing Network
Access Account credentials via SMB to HTTP relay, and the Erlang/OTP SSH exploit
everyone was excited about.

New module content (4)
Sante PACS Server Path Traversal (CVE-2025-2264)
Authors: Michael Heinzl and Tenable
Type: Auxiliary
Pull request: #20124</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
